JASMINE BROWN

A Patient Care Assistant with four years of experience, specializing in patient-centered care, diversity and inclusion, and team collaboration. A strong history of delivering empathetic care to diverse populations and building relationships with patients to foster positive outlooks.

123 Bridge Street,
Boston, MA 12345
j a sm i n eb rown@exa m ple.com
(123)456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PATIENT CARE ASSISTANT

Boston Medical Center, Boston, MA June 2019 - Present

- Deliver compassionate and empathetic care to diverse patients based on emotional, spiritual, and physical needs in a hospital with over 300+ beds, including building relationshipsand providing emotional support to drive positive outlooks
- Support RNsand the nurse manager in executing continuous improvement efforts to improve patient flow and triage amidst a 92% occupancy during Covid-19
- Monitor patient pain levels and vital signs, alert nurses to changes in patient condition and medical emergencies, and support activities of daily living (ADLs)

PATIENT CARE ASSISTANT

St. Luke's Hospital, Boston, MA August 2018 - June 2019

- Coordinated with medical teams to administer treatment plans, gather lab specimens, monitored patient symptoms, and ensured safe and efficient transport
- Supported patients with activities of daily living (ADLs), including nutrition, showering, toileting, dressing, and mobilization with a patient satisfaction rating of 95%

EDUCATION

High School Diploma Belmont High, Boston, MA September 2014 - June 2018

KEY SKILLS

- Di versi ty & I nd usi on
- ♦ Activities of Daily Living
- ♦ Relationship Building
- Patient Care
- Communication

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified NursingAssistant,
 Massachusetts Department of Public Health, 2018
- Basic Life Su p port (B LS), 2018